Where are you from?  Are?
London.
We are also coming to London very soon.  There we are coming
to WB Arena very soon.
Oh nice welcome Amashi.   Thank
you.  I will give you a pass, don't buy a ticket.   Hi Hi,
okay.  She will give this pass to her husband.  Don't
worry.
No she is not married.  Are you married?
I am married.
Purchase tickets sold online.
[laughter]
Look at this.   Is it made of
gold?  Hey, I didn't ask in a hurry.
[laughs] I did
n't ask, I mean, how will an unconscious person answer?
And you were not ashamed. I took
out the ring of an unconscious person and brought it. I took
out the ring from the finger of my original father and
brought it. What is an original father?
Your father's ISI mark is on him.
[laughs]
Why do you want a saree? You are looking better in these clothes.
My mother says that I look much better in these clothes. You
should not pay much attention to what mom and dad say. They look at you with love.
Look at us a lot,
but keep one thing in mind. I am
giving you one advice.  Never sit at home together.
Otherwise, someone might think that you will take off your clothes and
sit upside down.